Contact

Port Harcourt, Nigeria +2348167637212 (Home) etukanietie@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/etukanietie (LinkedIn) selar.co/m/etukanietie (Personal)

Top Skills

Data Analytics
Business Analytics
Entrepreneur

Certifications

B.Tech Computer Engineering

Etuk Anietie

Data Analytics Coach | Course Creator | Lead Instructor at SkillAhead Data Academy | Empowering Data Analysts for Success Nigeria

Summary

Anietie Etuk is a business developer, a data analyst and friend of children.

He is the Founder of CoreHead Business Solutions, TeenCoders and SkillAhead.

Currently, he is responsible for growth and business intelligence in these companies.

He works as the Data Analytics Head Coach at SkillAhead Academy responsible for developing the course materials, and training and supervising the team of over 10 instructors.

On average, every 3 months, he trains and certifies over 200 active data analysts.

By training, he is a certified Computer Engineer with expertise in data analytics, and proficiency in Python, MySQL, Power BI and Excel.

In business, he can lead any strategy or sales team.

Experience

SkillAhead

Lead Instructor

October 2022 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Port Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria

Register for my bootcamp http://www.skillahead.ng/data

TeenCoders

Founder

2014 - Present (10 years)

55 Olu-Obasanjo Road, Port Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria

Course Content Development

Business Development

CoreHead Business Solutions Ltd CEO

January 2012 - March 2023 (11 years 3 months)

Port Harcourt

Business Development and Consulting.

Quantum Business School Head Business Coach 2009 - 2011 (2 years)

Business Development, Strategic Consulting, including business plan & Development, Strategic Consulting business plan & Development

WealthLand Integrated Services
Strategist
September 2008 - September 2009 (1 year 1 month)
Investment Consultant, Portfolio Management

Next Business Centre Rivers State, Nigeria Manager January 2000 - January 2007 (7 years 1 month) Start-Up support Suggested new products that increased earnings.

Education

Rivers State University of Science and Technology B.Tech, Computer Engineering (2001 - 2006)

Rivers State University of Science and Technology, Port Harcourt, Rivers State

B.Tech, Computer Engineering · (2001 - 2006)